So, hopefully you've completed a welcome course, you had a look through the
well-being tips,
it might be a good idea to refresh these every now and again just so that you
know you're
looking out for yourself and you're checking in with your own well-being.
Please use this community, we are here to support you and it's one of the
things that
makes us special.
When we get together either in person or online, we can uplift and nourish each
other, which
is so important in this industry.
As a woman in general living in this patriarchal society, we'll come across
misogyny, we'll
come across people judging, comparing, having misconceptions about what it is
we do or even
who we are.
So, it's so important for you to check in with yourself, nourish yourself, care
for yourself
and we can help you to do that, the community is a big part of that.